I just want to go home.
Spaceman is a science fiction, adventure, drama film directed by Johan Renck.
Six months into a solo mission, a lonely astronaut confronts the cracks in his
marriage with help from a mysterious creature he discovers on his ship.
Jakub Procházka, played by Adam Sandler.
Hanuš (voice), played by Paul Dano.
Lenka Procházková, played by Carey Mulligan.
Peter, played by Kunal Nayyar.
Commissioner Tůmová, played by Isabella Rossellini.
Zdena, played by Lena Olin.
Spaceman is a 2024 American science fiction drama film
directed by Johan Renck and written by Colby Day.
It is based on the 2017 novel Spaceman of Bohemia by Jaroslav Kalfař.
Starring Adam Sandler, Carey Mulligan, Kunal Nayyar, Lena Olin, Isabella Rossellini, and Paul Dano, it follows an astronaut sent on
a mission to the edge of the Solar System who encounters a creature that helps him resolve his earthly problems.
Spaceman premiered at the 74th Berlin International Film Festival on February 21, 2024, and received a limited
theatrical release on February 23, 2024, before its streaming debut by Netflix on March 1, 2024.
The film received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, space
travel, space mission, alien, astronaut.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.